Oh, what are you doing?
あ、何してるの?
So why take it slow?
じゃあなんでゆっくりして
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It was pretty intense.
だいぶ激しかったね
Are you going home yet?
もう帰るの?
I see.
なるほど
Come once.
一回してきて
It's not very good though.
なかなかいいじゃないけど
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
what are you doing
何してる
of?
の?
I still feel like I haven't seen enough.
まだ 見足りないなと思って
I can't let you go home yet.
まだ帰らせないよ
Even though I do it all the time.
してばっかりなのに
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
Don't you want it again?
また欲しくなってきたんじゃない?
Just a little bit?
ちょっとだけ?
Are you starting to want it?
欲しくなってきた?
I slept like that.
あんなに寝てたのに
Have you ever done it with your clothes on?
服着たまましたことある?
There isn't.
ないよ
It's so twirling.
すごいくるくるしてるね
Can you turn around and look at the camera?
振り向いてカメラ見てもらう?
I'll put it in.
入れちゃうからな
Ah, I'm going in.
あー、入っちゃう
Also.
また
No, no, no.
ダメダメ
I really got into it.
めっちゃ入っちゃった
Did it really fit in?
め っちゃ入っちゃった?
It's in my hands.
うちの手ついてさ
Heal this.
これを癒して
The manjiru is amazing.
まんじるがすごい
No, not anymore.
やだ、もう
That's amazing.
すごいね
I won't be able to do it someday.
いつかもできなくて